{
    "id": "1612a2ea199444a6bb4e4b4ed844b589",
    "title": "Gap fills exercise (Vocabulary)",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "78df9ae1dcb44f22953ac8fb9ad633e9",
            "title": "Gap Fills Exercise (Vocabulary)",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I am tired of ..................... to your demands.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "satisfying",
                        "pandering",
                        "falling",
                        "meeting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In order to be successful, businesses have to …………………. to the needs of their customers.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cater",
                        "master",
                        "please",
                        "assimilate"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They tried to reassure me but I was still not able to ………………… my fears.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "prevent",
                        "annul",
                        "reduce",
                        "curtail"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I always preferred the …………………. of the big city.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "obscurity",
                        "anonymity",
                        "privileges"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The General ...................... the defeat to a series of tactical errors.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "blamed",
                        "pointed",
                        "ascribed",
                        "accredited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They cast ………………….. on his integrity.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "slanders",
                        "aspersions",
                        "remarks",
                        "skepticism"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A mugger ..................... him on the dark street.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "assailed",
                        "ascribed",
                        "hailed",
                        "treated"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Most people ………………….. to my views on the matter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "accept",
                        "approve",
                        "admit",
                        "assent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "My constant reassurance could not ..................... their fears.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "assuage",
                        "avoid",
                        "soothe",
                        "prevent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our plans have gone .........................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wrecked",
                        "awry",
                        "crooked",
                        "shattered"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}